# **Braian Bernatto**

React.js Frontend Developer

Asuncion, Paraguay (GMT-3) (+595) 983 709 234 <u>braian5353@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/braian-bernatto/

React.js Frontend Developer with 2+ years of experience. I've designed and developed web applications for public sectors as a Full-Stack web developer. Currently I'm focused on Frontend Development while working with a team and trying new challenges. I am continuously learning new things and aiming to excel in the programming field. I'm open to any kind of projects that could let me improve my skill set and have the experience of working with colleagues.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Tribunal Superior de Justicia Electoral**

React.js Full-Stack Developer — Mar, 2020 - Present

- I built a web application to control contract balances of government tenders that gives instant visual reports and avoids errors by 90% in the execution of these contracts. The app has jwt authentication and a dynamic UI for normal and admin users.
- I built a date and days calculator web application with a list of holidays of Paraguay that speeds up the control process by 80% for many departments.

Tech Stack: Next.js - TailwindCSS - Node.js - Express - PostgreSQL - Strapi - Chart.js - JWT.

JavaScript Full-Stack Developer — Jan, 2019 - Feb, 2020

• I developed a string generator web application with CRUD operations and authentication that reduced the amount of typos by 90% in the elaboration of critical documents.

Tech Stack: EJS - CSS - JS - Node.js - Express - PostgreSQL.

# **PROJECTS**

**Eagle Eye Website** 

React.js Full-Stack Developer - https://eagleeye.com.py - Aug, 2022 - Sep, 2022

• I built a multilingual website featured with a contact form for a soccer related business that improves the image of the brand and promotes their services and achievements.

Tech Stack: Next.js - Google Maps API - Netlify forms - Custom HTML5 Theme - next-translate.

#### SKILLS

Programming Languages: Advanced: JavaScript; Intermediate: SQL.

Frameworks Tools: Advanced: React.js, Next.js.

Data Base: Advanced: PostgreSQL; Intermediate: MongoDB.

Languages: Intermediate: English; Native: Spanish.

## **EDUCATION**

UTIC – Asunción. Computer Science And Programming – Apr, 2018